#### ANGELLA KYABANA

MOBILE: 0785027936 Email: <a href="mailto:kyabanaangella@gmail.com">kyabanaangella@gmail.com</a>

### **Personal Profile Statement**

Am a hard-working lady, an enthusiastic pursuer of opportunity to work with teams, keen on achievements and lessons to learn from every work of experience and able to complete tasks under minimum supervision. With a strong drive to see things through completion.

# **Career Objective.**

To build a career in a growing organization, where I can get the opportunities to prove my abilities by accepting challenges and fulfilling the organization goal and climbing the career ladder through continuous learning and commitment.

### **Achievements**

- More than two years of relevant work experience
- Star employee of the month (2023

### Education

2019-2022	Degree in mass communication in	journalism Uganda Martyrs University, Mbarara
2017-2018	UACE	Aisha Girls' High school
2012- 2016	UCE	Aisha Girls High School

## **Employment**

YEAR	WORK	ORGANIZATION	RESPONSIBILITIES
2023 June update	Receptionist	Hannah Salon	Day to day revenue
			balancing
			Welcoming new
			customers
2023 Jan- Aug	Graphic Designer and	Kworo Investiments	Scheduling my Boss's
	Office administrator		meetings
			Designing posters and
			stickers

2022-2023	Production editor and Administrator	Native Voices	Editing news Scripts and balancing company day to day expenses.
February 2021- May 2021	TV presenter	Bunyoro TV	Discussing life experiences and visiting different hospitals in Homia
June 2021 - December	Radio Presenter	Mercy FM	Politics program and Entertainment
January 2020 –June	Adult Education	Light House	English Teacher

### **Personal Skill.**

- Self-motive and a good team player
- Ability to perform under Pressure and meet deadline.
- Quick and always eager to learn new ideas.

### Declaration.

I solemnly declare that all the above information is correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.